(Lee Jae In, Kim Woo Seok, Choi Ye Bin)
(Cha Woo Min, An Ji Ho, Jung So Ri)
(Scriptwriter: Kang Min Ji)
(Director: Im Dae Woong)
(Night Has Come)
(All people, organizations,
locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Night has come.)
("Murder of a White Butterfly")
(Yooil High School)
- It's not me.
- Hey, guys.
- It's really not me.
- Stop lying. It's you.
- Why won't you listen to me? Gosh.
- Seriously. She has to be it.
- Are you for real?
- Hey.
- I told you it wasn't me!
- It has to be you. Come on.
- Just think. If I were the Mafia,
- I know it's you!
- why did I help you...
- Come on.
When you were suspected?
- It's not that! I...
- Seriously. Heo Yul is the Mafia.
- It's you.
- All right.
- Okay. All right.
- Right.
The innocent citizens have
lost, and the Mafia has won!
- Yes!
- What?
- I told you I was a citizen!
- Gosh.
You just won't believe me.
- You carried this game.
- You said you were a citizen!
- I told you he was the Mafia.
- It was you?
- Let's play another one.
- Okay. Let's play again.
- They're so loud.
- Hurry.
Starting with the next game...
- I have my eyes on you now.
- Losers going to buy...
snacks this time. Are you in?
- I'm in!
- Darn it.
- Hey.
- Let's start now.
Tell them to shut their mouths.
Heo Yul will be the first
one I kill in the next round.
- Hey!
- Hurry.
Kyung Jun is sleeping right now.
You're so loud.
Those jerks.
Hey, stop it.
Hey, Na Hee.
Don't talk to Na Hee.
You'll get chewed out again.
Hey. Switch. Come on, do it.
He likes her. Switch seats with him.
Hey. Doesn't he look gorgeous or what?
This belongs in a magazine, doesn't it?
How can he look this gorgeous?
I'll tell Jun Hee tomorrow that
you secretly took a photo of him.
Could you please do that? Let
me seduce him while we're at it.
You've been saying that since last year.
When will you do it?
- You can do it now.
- I'll do it soon.
- Jun Hee.
- Stop it.
Look at this.
Why don't you just sit next to him
if you're going to stare at him?
I wasn't staring.
(Game Development Contest)
(Yooil High School, Class 2-3)
Hello, Ms. Kim.
- Did you find it?
- What?
- Right now, I'm...
- Hello.
- What did you say?
- I can't...
- Hello? No.
- Can you not hear me?
- I can't hear you well. Hello?
- Should we go?
- Sure.
- What?
- Hey, Hyun Ho. Can you help me?
- Only our class arrived?
Give me that.
I...
Hey.
Have we been here before? Why
do I feel like I've been here?
Retreat centers are all the same.
Hey, Lee Yoon Seo.
- I'm going inside.
- Okay.
- Yoon Seo.
- What?
What are you doing? Let's go inside.
Okay.
Darn it. This is so annoying.
(Scan the QR code to connect to Wi-Fi...)
(and to install the retreat
center's facility app.)
Still haven't decided on
your birthday present?
You'd better tell me by today.
I won't buy you a thing if
you tell me past midnight.
Good grief. You're so petty.
But I still haven't decided yet.
A mystery novel?
- Yes. That.
- Okay.
Gosh. You and mystery novels.
My phone isn't getting any reception.
Is this normal here?
Excuse me. Can I make a phone call?
The phone line is down now.
What should I do? Should I go to them?
(Welcome to Muryeong Retreat Center.)
Oh, my.
Look at So Mi flirting. Seriously.
- Hey.
- What?
Stop staring at him.
You're making it obvious.
I wasn't staring at him.
As if.
(Guide Map of Muryeong Retreat Center)
This is so lame.
I can make this in a day.
What are you talking about?
You didn't scan the QR code?
It was installed automatically.
Give me your phone. I'll do it for you.
What? No.
I can read this.
Do you want to carry that
with you for two whole days?
- Class President.
- Yes.
I need to go and pick up the
students in other classes.
Don't do anything. Just stay in your rooms.
Keep an eye on your class,
so they don't cause trouble.
Okay. I will.
- Help him, Vice President.
- Okay.
Once I come back, we have to
take a group picture at night.
Tell them to keep their uniforms on.
- Okay.
- I'm leaving now.
Okay.
What's going on? Why is he so busy?
Wi-Fi isn't working here.
This place is awful.
But why are we taking a
group picture at night?
Who knows?
I'm not getting any signals at all.
(The phone is out of the service area.)
Hey. He's filming us again.
Seriously. He has high standards.
He's not filming us. It's just me.
What can I do? It's all my fault.
Get over yourself. Seriously.
Come on. What is this?
- What's going on?
- What is this?
Hey, turn on the lights.
What are you doing?
- What is it?
- What?
What's going on?
- Quit joking around.
- Come on.
- Are you serious?
- Gosh.
- Hey.
- You!
He's so annoying.
- Come on.
- Gosh.
- Darn it. That lunatic.
- What was that?
Hey, listen carefully.
Here's what I heard here.
A long time ago, a high school
girl killed herself here.
So there are a few things
you must not do here.
Don't look in the mirror
and turn around at midnight.
And if someone grabs your
ankle when you're sleeping,
don't look down.
If you break these rules,
a ghost will pop up!
- Hey!
- Get lost. That crazy jerk!
What?
- You lunatic.
- Come on.
Are you scared?
Stop that.
- Let's go back to our room.
- Okay.
Hey.
When can you give my money back?
I need to pay the tuition at the academy.
Ju Won.
Don't be like that. We're friends.
I told you I was going
to pay you interest too.
Give me some more time.
- I need it by next...
- Shut it! Darn you, jerk.
Are you a loan shark?
We're here on a retreat. Why
are you asking us for money?
Did you do sports betting again? Did you?
Da Bum. Did you lend them money too?
What?
Yes.
But I can wait for my money.
There's no rush.
How much is the total?
I'll pay you back.
In return,
play basketball with me. Are you in?
(Unable to connect to the Internet)
I need to watch a special
lecture on coding online.
Why isn't it working?
What are you doing?
Gosh. You teased me for reading a book.
Hey. Who studies on a school trip?
Don't make it so obvious
that you're first in class.
That's why they tease
you and call you Mensa.
Mensa is the name of a society.
The members of the society
are called Mensans.
How many times must I tell you that?
(Installing)
What's this?
I told you I didn't need this.
It wasn't me.
(Welcome.)
(The Mafia Game will begin now.
Check your identity.)
(Lee Yoon Seo, your identity is a citizen.)
What's this?
I'm a citizen.
- What about you?
- Me too.
(Main Menu: Chat, Vote, Rules,
Voting Status, Participants)
(The participants' identities
will secretly be assigned.)
(The identities...)
(are citizens, doctors, police
officers, and the Mafia.)
(A doctor can prevent a participant
of choice from getting executed.)
(the occupation of a selected participant.)
(the identity of a selected participant.)
(The participants have
from 8am to midnight...)
(to ferret out the Mafia through a vote.)
(At midnight, the one with the
most votes will be executed.)
What's this?
(And the executed participant's
identity will be disclosed.)
(After the vote at midnight, )
(all the participants excluding
the Mafia will go to sleep.)
Ju Won. Let me give this a shot.
Stand right there.
Here it goes.
(When the participants are
asleep during the night, )
(the Mafia has until 6am...)
Don't move.
(to execute the participant personally.)
(When the participants are
asleep during the night, )
(the Mafia has until 6am...)
Mafia?
What's this about?
What the heck is this?
(If Team Citizens or Team Mafia...)
(wipes out the other team and wins, )
(the game is over.)
(Citizens, doctors and police are a team.)
(All participants, )
(identify the Mafia, and begin to vote.)
(Hi, losers.)
Is it my turn to step out?
Hi, losers. Let's play a game.
(Is Baek Eun Ha...)
Is Baek Eun Ha the mafia?
Look at this jerk. He's so happy.
Hey. I can't stand him.
Let's kill him.
All votes on him? Are you in?
- I'm in.
Okay.
Heo Yul is the mafia.
Let's kill Heo Yul.
Okay.
(Do you want to vote for Heo Yul?)
(Yes.)
(Im Eun Chan voted for Heo Yul.)
I voted by pressing the name.
Really?
(Do you want to vote for Heo Yul?)
(Lee Yoon Seo voted for Heo Yul.)
We never signed up,
but how does this know our names?
There's no internet connection.
How are we playing this game?
What? Are they still not here yet?
Our teacher's gone for a while.
Do you think they are all right?
What if they got into an accident?
Jun Hee.
Do you know when our teacher will be back?
No, I couldn't reach him.
Do you get receptions?
No.
What about the staff?
I think they all left with him.
There's no one.
What? What do we do?
How long do we have to wait?
There must be a phone in the office.
Let's go check.
Sure.
(Iced coffee)
It's out.
This coffee is new.
Are you sure you saw nobody?
Yes, I didn't see anyone.
Hello?
It's disconnected.
Try 112 or 119.
Okay.
(Kim So Mi)
Lee Yoon Seo. Come to the swimming
pool in the other building now.
It's urgent.
Do you know what's going on?
Well...
We're all taking turns
to record an interview...
to play during the event tomorrow.
How can we have an
interview in this situation?
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Ju Won.
Where are you going?
Oh, well...
Other kids wanted to see me.
Let me talk to him for a second.
But...
- Let's go.
- But...
It's okay. Come on.
It's my turn.
Hey...
- Yes!
Hey.
What are you doing?
- Jin Da Bum, get up.
- What?
Get up now.
Goodness.
- Kyung Jun.
- Yes?
Don't you think your joke crossed the line?
My joke?
But I couldn't be more serious right now.
Da Bum said he'd help us
prepare for the event tomorrow.
Can I take him with me?
- I'm taking him.
- But I...
I'm okay.
He said he's okay.
Gosh, that prick.
You think you're so handsome?
Stop getting on my nerves.
Darn it. Who was that?
Seung Bin, you got so big.
Have you been working out?
Jang Hyun Ho, you jerk.
Why are you causing a ruckus here?
To exercise.
What? You got a problem?
You couldn't even become national athletes.
Fine. Exercise all you want.
(Jang Hyun Ho)
- Let's go.
- That jerk.
Those jerks...
Stop.
Don't do it.
Are you okay?
Hide.
Hey, you're here. Why don't you go in?
Yoon Seo, you should go first.
Okay.
They'll start recording
when Yoon Seo enters.
We should wait.
Why put so much effort?
- Hey.
- Oh, my gosh.
Surprise!
- Happy birthday to you
Dear Yoon Seo - Dear Yoon Seo
Imagine this is a candle and blow it out.
Why are you doing this?
You never talked to her before.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
This is what friends are for.
I even got you a gift.
Birthday noogies!
- Hey.
- Are you ready?
Throw her or not?
- I'm throwing her.
- Stop it.
Let's do it.
- Throw her or what?
- Put her down.
She's going to cry.
That was mean, wasn't it?
Happy birthday.
Are you crazy? Why did you push her?
Yoon Seo, are you okay?
I'm okay.
- Hurry up. I can't go.
- You go.
Go save her.
Yoon Seo.
Yoon Seo!
- Help...
- Do something!
Darn it.
Hurry up and help him.
Are you okay?
Yoon Seo!
- Are you okay?
- Help me carry her.
I think we went too far.
Will she be okay?
Yoon Seo, are you okay?
Are you in pain?
- No, I'm okay.
- Hold on.
Why do you still look like that?
You should've changed
your clothes at least.
I waited for you to wake up.
Do you know how worried I was?
I thought you were going to die.
What happened?
I don't know.
What's this?
Nothing.
- Are you okay now?
- What?
You quit swimming because you
couldn't enter water anymore.
Let me go. Don't touch me.
Seung Heon.
Oh, about that...
It's okay. I'm over it now.
Really?
I should gather everyone and talk to them.
- Take some rest.
- Okay.
Apologize to Yoon Seo.
Birthday noogies?
Don't you think you took it too far?
Sorry.
We only...
wanted to celebrate your birthday.
It's okay. Don't cry.
Really? Will you forgive me?
Yes.
I'm sorry, Yoon Seo.
It's fine.
- Go and check what's going on.
- They will be here in a minute.
They're back.
Jun Hee, what now?
We can't reach them, and
we get no reception here.
He's right. What are we going to do?
Let's sleep in our rooms for now.
I'll check again early
in the morning tomorrow.
Okay.
Let's go.
Guys, sleep in your rooms.
Stop wasting your time here.
Right. Go to sleep for now.
Jun Hee and I will go
check outside tomorrow.
- Let's go to bed.
- Go to your rooms.
Yes, go to your rooms.
Kim So Mi was faking it.
Let it slide. She said sorry.
She keeps doing that because
you keep letting her get away.
What can I do about it?
Gosh, I hate that girl.
You promised to play all night long.
You still feel like playing
after what happened?
Just go to bed.
A minute left to vote.
What's this?
(Remaining time)
There's even an announcement.
This is brilliant. Do you approve?
Yes, but you made it.
- No.
- Hey, what is this?
Did you see that?
Isn't this brilliant?
- He made it.
- It wasn't me.
Did you vote?
- Yes.
- Who did you vote for?
Heo Yul?
The voting has ended.
I bet he got all the votes.
You made this anyway.
What did I do?
Besides, why did you vote for me?
Don't make this boring.
See?
Heo Yul with the most votes,
24 votes will be executed.
- What? He got the most votes?
- Bye.
There he goes again.
Cut it out.
Are you acting again?
It's boring. Stop it.
What's going on?
What's wrong?
Hey, what's wrong?
- What's wrong?
- Are you okay?
Is he okay?
Yul, I said that's enough.
What the...
- What's going on?
- Hey.
What are you doing?
- Stop it.
- What are you doing?
- What's he doing?
- Hey.
- Stop.
What on earth is your problem?
- Yul.
- Stop!
That's enough.
- What's wrong with him?
- Somebody stop him.
What are you doing?
- Stop.
- What was that for?
- No.
- Yul!
Yul.
What is wrong with Yul?
- No! Oh, no!
- Hey.
Heo Yul was a Citizen.
- What just happened?
- What is going on?
(Night Has Come)
(Gwangju Information and Content Agency)
(This content was produced through
Gwangju Information and...)
(Content Agency's 2022 OTT Platform
Content Production Business.)